A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, International Centers and Institutes FA1133
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller Foundation records, International Centers and Institutes
1969-1984
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller Foundation
International Laboratory for Research on Animal Diseases
Consultative Group on International Agricultural Research
International Center for Living Aquatic Resources Management
Centro Internacional de Agricultura Tropical
FA1133
21.41 Cubic Feet 39 legal document boxes, 3 half legal document boxes and 3 flat folders
Conditions Governing Access
Records more than 10 years old are open for research with select materials restricted as noted. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC. Researchers interested in accessing digital media (floppy disks, CDs, DVDs, etc.) or audiovisual material (audio cassettes, VHS, etc.) in this collection must use an access surrogate. The original items may not be accessed because of preservation concerns. To request an access surrogate be made, or if you are unsure if there is an access surrogate, please contact an archivist.
Scope and Contents
Types of records include: correspondence, reports, photographs, newspaper articles, and oversized architectural plans.
Biographical / Historical
International Laboratory for Research on Animal Diseases (ILRAD) was established in Nairobi in 1973 by agreement between the Government of Kenya and the Rockefeller Foundation acting for the Consultative Group on International Agricultural Research. The mandate of the Laboratory is to develop safe, effective and economically feasible control measures for livestock diseases which seriously limit world food production.
International Center for Living Aquatic Resources Management (ICLARM) was organized in 1975 and incorporated in 1977 in the Philippines where it maintains its headquarters. The Rockefeller Foundation developed the concept leading to ICLARM, and remains its principal donor. The rationale behind the Rockefeller initiative was that there appeared to be a need in fisheries for an organization similar to the international agricultural centers which operate under the aegis of the Consultative Group on International Agricultural Research (CGIAR). It would be an organization that could conduct long-term coordinated research on the principal fisheries problems in the developing world.
International Center for Tropical Agriculture (CIAT) was backed by the Colombian government and Rockefeller, Ford, and Kellogg Foundations, CIAT was formally established in 1967 and began its research in 1969. While aware of the many constraints to farming in the tropics, CIAT's founders saw this vast region as a world of promise, where agriculture, with the aid of modern science, might contribute substantially to reducing hunger and poverty. Since no single organization can address the whole of tropical agriculture, CIAT complements the efforts of others by focusing on selected crops and research areas.
Technical Advisory Committee (TAC) was created to support the activities of CGIAR. Located in Rome, Italy and composed of a small number of independent scientists in disciplines related to agricultural development.
Consultantive Group on International Agricultural Research (CGIAR) is a global research partnership for a food-secure future. CGIAR science is dedicated to reducing poverty, enhancing food and nutrition security, and improving natural resources and ecosystem services. Its research is carried out by 15 CGIAR centers in close collaboration with hundreds of partners, including national and regional research institutes, civil society organizations, academia, development organizations and the private sector.
Arrangement
Series 1-International Laboratory for Research and Animal Diseases (ILRAD)
Series 2-International Center for Living Aquatic Resources Management (ICLARM)
Series 3-International Center for Tropical Agriculture (CIAT)
Series 4-Technical Advisory Committee (TAC)
Series 5-Consultative Group on International Agricultural Research (CGIAR)
- International Laboratory for Research and Animal Diseases (ILRAD), 1970-1981; 1; 7.52 Cubic Feet 11 legal document boxes and 3 flat file folders
  - Board of Trustees, Meeting, 1973 November 26-27 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Board of Trustees, Minutes, 1974-1979 (Box 1, Folder 2-3)
  - Board of Trustees, Meeting, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 4-5)
  - Board of Trustees, Meeting, 1979 April 23-25 (Box 1, Folder 4A)
    Conditions Governing Access
    Restricted from access - Confidential material
  - Board of Trustees, Meeting, Nominating Committee, 1980 March 18-26 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Board of Trustees, Minutes & Appendices, 1980 March 18-26, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Board of Trustees, Meeting, Other Committees, 1980 March 18-26 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Board of Trustees, Back Minutes, 1979-1980 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Board of Trustees, Executive Committee, Meeting & Minutes, 1974-1979 (Box 2, Folder 10-11)
  - Board of Trustees, Executive Committee, Meeting, 1979 August 29-31 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Board of Trustees, Executive Committee, Meeting-Reports, 1979 August 29-31 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Board of Trustees, Executive Committee, Meeting, 1980 March, 1979-1980 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Board of Trustees, Members, 1973-1981 (Box 3, Folder 15-16)
  - Institute of International Education (IIE) Contract, International Personnel, 1970, 1972-1975 (Box 3, Folder 17-18)
  - Library and Librarian, 1976-1977 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Recruitment of Administrative Officer, 1976-1978 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Recruitment of Administrative Officer, 1976-1978 (Box 3, Folder 20A)
  - Capital Construction Programme, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Capital Construction Programme, ILRAD-Plans and Elevations, 1975; 2016:FA1133:001 (Folder 1)
  - Architectural Drawings of Building in Nairobi (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Architectural Drawings of Nairobi, 2016:FA1133:002 (Folder 2)
  - Architectural Brief for the International Laboratory on Animal Diseases, Nairobi, Kenya, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Architectural Brief for the International Laboratory on Animal Diseases, Nairobi, Kenya, 2016:FA1133:003 (Folder 1)
  - Building Program, 1974-1975 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Building Program, Architects Brief, 1974-1975 (Box 4, Folder 25-26)
  - Building Program, Architects Brief, 1974-1975; 2016:FA1133:004 (Folder 3)
  - USAID Grant for 1974, 1974-1975, 1977-1978 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Vehicles, 1974-1975 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Starnes, Ordway, Correspondence, 1974-1975 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Programme and Budget, 1980-1981 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Research and Training Activities, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Photographs and Negatives, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Inauguration of the International Laboratory Research on Animal Diseases, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Articles, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Sadun, Elvio, Plaque, 1974, 1977-1978 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Sadun, Elvio H., Memorials, 1974-1975, 1977-1978 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Suggestions for Director, Board, and Staff, 1972-1973 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Suggestions for Director, Board, and Staff, 1972-1973 (Box 5, Folder 37A)
  - Search Committee, For Elvio H. Sadun's Successor, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 38-39)
  - Search Committee, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Henson, James B., Director, 1974-1975 (Box 6, Folder 41-42)
  - Search Committee, James B. Henson's Successor, 1977-1978 (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - Search Committee, James B. Henson's Successor, 1977-1978 (Box 7, Folder 43A)
  - Search Committee, Vol. I, 1977-1978 (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - Search Committee, Vol. I, 1977-1978 (Box 7, Folder 44A)
  - Search Committee, Vol. II, 1977-1978 (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - Search Committee, Short List, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - Search Committee, Short Short List, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 47)
  - Search Committee, Short Short List, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 47A)
  - Additional Applications for Director, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 48)
  - Additional Applications for Director, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 48A)
  - Announcements for A. C. Allison as Director, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 49)
  - Interim Arrangements for Period between James B. Henson & A. C. Allison, 1978 June-October (Box 8, Folder 50)
  - Allison, A. C., Director, 1978-1980 (Box 8, Folder 51)
  - Allison, A. C., Director, 1978-1980 (Box 8, Folder 51A)
  - Search Committee, A. C. Allison's Successor, 1978, 1980-1981 (Box 8, Folder 52)
  - Search Committee, A. C. Allison's Successor, 1978, 1980-1981 (Box 8, Folder 52A)
  - Interim Arrangements between A. C. Allison as Director and his Successor, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 53)
  - Mitoko, M. H., 1974, 1976-1978 (Box 8, Folder 54)
  - Henson, James B.-John A. Pino, Correspondence, 1976-1978, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 55-57)
  - Discussions in Amsterdam, 1980 February 11 (Box 9, Folder 58)
  - Memoranda of Announcement & Articles of Association, 1973-1975 (Box 9, Folder 59)
  - Accounting to Consultative Group on International Agricultural Research (CGIAR) from RF and ILRAD Initial Fund, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 60)
  - Land Use, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 61)
  - Land Use, 1974; 2016:FA1133:005 (Folder 3)
  - Dalgliesh Marshall, Architects, Robert P. Marshall, 1974-1975 (Box 9, Folder 62)
  - Construction Program, Architects and Quantity Surveyors, 1974, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 63)
  - Application to the Internal Revenue Service, 1974-1975 (Box 10, Folder 64)
  - Budgets and Construction Costs, 1973-1974 (Box 10, Folder 65)
  - Termination of Rockefeller Foundation as Executing Agency, 1975-1977 (Box 10, Folder 66)
  - Scientific Advisory Committee, 1977-1979 (Box 10, Folder 67)
  - Pino, John A., Correspondence with Board Members, 1979-1981 (Box 10, Folder 68)
  - Pino, John A.-Peter C. Nderito, Management Problems, 1978-1979 (Box 10, Folder 69)
  - Logo and Letterhead (Box 10, Folder 70)
  - Progress Report and Budget Presentation, 1974 June (Box 10, Folder 71)
  - Proposal for an International Laboratory for Research on Animal Diseases, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 72)
  - East Coast Fever and Related Diseases: A Technical Confernce, 1971 March 8 (Box 10, Folder 73)
  - An International Laboratory for Animal Disease Research in Africa, 1970 Novmeber (Box 10, Folder 74)
  - Livestock Production in Tropical Africa, 1970 November (Box 10, Folder 75)
  - Meeting on Livestock Improvement and Disease Control, 1971 January 8-9 (Box 11, Folder 76)
  - An International African Livestock Center Task Force Report, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 77)
  - Animal Production and Animal Research in Tropical Africa, 1972 September (Box 11, Folder 78)
  - Donors, 1973-1979 (Box 11, Folder 79)
  - United Nations Development Programme Support, 1977-1978 (Box 11, Folder 80)
  - Reports, 1971-1973 (Box 11, Folder 81)
- International Center for Living Aquatic Resources Management (ICLARM), 1973-1984; 2; 2.9 Cubic Feet 4 legal document boxes, 1 half-legal box and 1 flat file folder
  - Annual Meeting, 1976 November 3, 1976-1977 (Box 12, Folder 82)
  - Executive Committee, Meeting, 1977 January 28 (Box 12, Folder 83)
  - Annual Meeting, Board of Trustees, 1977 November 2, 1977-1978 (Box 12, Folder 84)
  - Board of Trustees, Meeting, 1978 March 18, 1978-1979 (Box 12, Folder 85)
  - Executive Committee, Meeting, 1978 July 14 (Box 12, Folder 86)
  - Annual Meeting, 1978 November 1 (Box 12, Folder 87)
  - Board of Trustees, Meeting, 1979 November 15 (Box 12, Folder 88)
  - Annual Meeting, 1980 November 12-October 25-26 (Box 13, Folder 89-91)
  - Board of Trustees, Meeting, 1983 November 8-10 (Box 13, Folder 92)
  - Materials for James E. Johnston, 1979-1980 (Box 14, Folder 93)
  - Aquaculture Meeting, 1980 May 5-10, 1973, 1978-1980 (Box 14, Folder 94)
  - General Correspondence, 1977, 1980-1981 (Box 14, Folder 95)
  - General Correspondence, The CLSU Freshwater Aquaculture Center Development Plan and BFAR Facilities, 1977, 1980-1981; 2016:FA1133:006 (Folder 3)
  - Agency for International Development (AID), 1980-1982 (Box 14, Folder 96)
  - Fisheries, 1982-1984 (Box 14, Folder 97)
  - Financial Information, 1977-1978, 1981-1982 (Box 14, Folder 98)
  - Proposal for the Creation of an International Center for Living Aquatic Resources Management, 1974 January (Box 15, Folder 99)
  - Application for IRS Ruling, 1977-1978, 1981-1982 (Box 15, Folder 100-101)
  - Incorporation and Decree, 1976-1978 (Box 15, Folder 102)
  - Board of Trustees, 1975-1982 (Box 15, Folder 103)
  - Rockefeller Foundation Support, 1976-1977 (Box 15, Folder 104)
  - Non-Rockefeller Foundation Financial Support, 1976-1977 (Box 15, Folder 105)
  - Personnel Policies, 1973, 1975-1976 (Box 15, Folder 106)
  - Personnel, 1978-1979 (Box 15, Folder 107)
  - Marr, John C., Director General, 1974, 1976-1979 (Box 15, Folder 108)
  - Steinbach, H. Burr, Trustee, 1976-1979 (Box 16, Folder 109)
  - Day, Maxwell F. C., Trustee, 1976-1980 (Box 16, Folder 110)
  - Annual Report from Director General, 1983-1984 (Box 16, Folder 111)
  - Fundraising, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 112)
- International Center for Tropical Agriculture (CIAT), 1969, 1972, 1974, 1984; 3; 1.02 Cubic Feet 1 half-legal box and 1 flat file folder
  - International Center for Tropical Agriculture, Headquarters Development, 1969 November 10 (Box 17, Folder 113)
  - International Center for Tropical Agriculture, Headquarters Development, 1969; 2016:FA1133:007 (Folder 3)
  - Director General Search, 1972, 1974, 1984 (Box 17, Folder 114-115)
- Technical Advisory Committee (TAC), 1971-1981; 4; 2.35 Cubic Feet 5 legal document boxes
  - Meeting, 1971 June 29-July 2 (Box 18, Folder 116)
  - Meeting, Bibliography, 1971 June 29-July 2 (Box 18, Folder 117)
  - Meeting, 1971 October 19-22-1972 April 10-13 (Box 18, Folder 118-120)
  - Meeting, 1972 August 2-4-1973 July 25-August 3 (Box 19, Folder 121-124)
  - Meeting, 1974 February 4-8, 1973-1974 (Box 19, Folder 125)
  - Meeting, 1974 July 24-August 2, 1974-1975 (Box 19, Folder 126)
  - Meeting, 1975 July 22-26, 1974-1975 (Box 20, Folder 127)
  - Meeting, 1975 July 22-26, Reports (Box 20, Folder 128-129)
  - Meeting, 1975 October 27-28 (Box 20, Folder 130)
  - Meeting, 1976 February 2-6, 1973-1976 (Box 20, Folder 131)
  - Meeting, 1976 May 8-13 (Box 20, Folder 132)
  - Meeting, 1976 October 14-18, 1976-1977 (Box 21, Folder 133)
  - Meeting, 1977 January 31-February 4-September 9-10 (Box 21, Folder 134-136)
  - Meeting, 1978 February 14-21, 1977-1978 (Box 21, Folder 137-138)
  - Meeting, 1978 June 6-13 (Box 21, Folder 139)
  - Meeting, 1978 September 20-22-1980 January (Box 22, Folder 140-143)
  - Meeting, 1981 February 24-March 3, 1979-1981 (Box 22, Folder 144)
- Consultative Group on International Agricultural Research (CGIAR), 1969-1982; 5; 9.18 Cubic Feet 9 legal document boxes and 1 half-legal box
  - Discussions, Establishment of Consortium on International Agricultural Research, 1970-1971 (Box 23, Folder 145)
  - Institute Week, 1970 September 28-October 2 (Box 23, Folder 146)
  - Pre-Consultative Group Meeting, 1971 January 14-15 (Box 23, Folder 147)
  - Consultative Group Meeting, 1971 May 19-December 3-4 (Box 23, Folder 148-149)
  - Consultative Group Meeting, 1971 December 3-4, 1971-1972 (Box 23, Folder 150)
  - Consultative Group Meeting, 1972 November 1-2, 1972-1973 (Box 23, Folder 151)
  - Consultative Group Meeting, 1972 November 1-2, 1972-1973 (Box 24, Folder 152)
  - Consultative Group Meeting, 1973 November 1-2, 1973-1974 (Box 24, Folder 153)
  - Consultative Group Meeting, 1974 July 29-August 4 (Box 24, Folder 154-156)
  - Consultative Group Meeting, 1974 October 30-31-1975 October 30-31 (Box 25, Folder 157-159)
  - Consultative Group Meeting, 1975 October 30-31, 1975-1976 (Box 25, Folder 160)
  - Consultative Group Meeting, 1976 October 27-29 (Box 25, Folder 161)
  - Consultative Group Meeting, 1977 November 16-17, 1977-1978 (Box 25, Folder 162)
  - International Centers' Week, 1971 October 5-8 (Box 25, Folder 163)
  - International Centers' Week, 1972 July 30-August 4-1973 July 30-August 4 (Box 26, Folder 164-168)
  - International Centers' Week, 1974 July 30-August 2, Memoranda from Secretariat, 1982 (Box 26, Folder 167)
  - International Centers' Week, 1974-1976 (Box 27, Folder 170-174)
  - International Centers' Week, 1977-1978 November 6-10 (Box 28, Folder 175-179)
  - International Centers' Week, 1978 November 8-10, 1978-1979 (Box 28, Folder 180)
  - International Centers' Week, 1978 November 8-10, 1978-1979 (Box 29, Folder 181)
  - International Centers' Week, 1979 October-November-1980 October 27-31 (Box 29, Folder 182-185)
  - International Centers' Week, 1980 October 27-31-1982 November 8-12 (Box 30, Folder 186-189)
  - Bellagio, 1969 April 23-25-1970 December 3-4, 1972 May 17-19 (Box 31, Folder 191-196)
  - Bellagio, 1974 March 19-21, 1973-1974 (Box 31, Folder 197)
  - Bellagio, 1975 June 1-4 (Box 32, Folder 198)
  - Draft Summary, Proceedings, International Centers' Week, 1974 July 29-August 2 (Box 32, Folder 199)
  - Agricultural Research Activities, 1974 (Box 32, Folder 200)
  - International Food Policy Research Institute, Meeting, 1974 (Box 32, Folder 201)
  - United Nations Development Programme, Social & Economic Implications of Large-Scale Introduction of New Varieties of Food Grains, 1974 October (Box 32, Folder 202)
  - CGIAR Booklet, Draft (Box 32, Folder 203)
  - Evaluation of Caris Pilot Project, Preliminary Report, 1974 (Box 32, Folder 204)
  - Appraisal of Livestock Project, Mali, 1974 October 4 (Box 32, Folder 205)
  - Ford Memorandum, Rural Development in China and Miscellaneous Agricultural Matters, 1975 (Box 32, Folder 206)
  - Proposal for the Review of the CGIAR System, 1975 October 10 (Box 33, Folder 207)
  - International Fertilizer Development Center, 1975 (Box 33, Folder 208)
  - Pino, John A,, Diary-CGIAR, 1975 October 30-31 (Box 33, Folder 209)
  - Nominations to the Board of Trustees of CIP and the Governing Board of ICRISAT, 1975 (Box 33, Folder 210)
  - Tropical Products Institute, Vol. 1: Summary and Overall Conclusions, 1975 (Box 33, Folder 211)
  - Tropical Products Institute, Vol. 2: The Oilseed Crops, 1975 (Box 33, Folder 212)
  - Tropical Products Institute, Vol. 3: The Fibre Crops, Hides and Skins and Leather, 1975 (Box 33, Folder 213)
  - ICARDA Subcommittee Meeting, 1975 February 10-11 (Box 33, Folder 214)
  - Related Materials, International Centers' Week, 1975 July 23-August 1 (Box 33, Folder 215)
  - Meeting of Institute Directors, 1973 February 11-16 (Box 33, Folder 216)
  - Ford Foundation Memorandum, Programs and Budgets of the International Agricultural Centers, 1974 (Box 33, Folder 217)
  - Nominations to the Board of Trustees, 1976 (Box 33, Folder 218)
  - ICRISAT Capital Plan, 1975 (Box 33, Folder 219)
  - International Centre on Insect Physiology and Ecology (ICIPE) Visit, 1976 (Box 33, Folder 220)
  - Memoranda, 1976 September-October (Box 33, Folder 221)
  - Priorities for International Support to Agricultural Research in Developing Countries, 1976 (Box 33, Folder 222)
  - Accounting and Budgeting, 1975 (Box 34, Folder 223)
  - International Buffalo Research Needs, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 224)
  - Statements by Director Generals, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 225)
  - General Correspondence, 1975-1976 (Box 34, Folder 226)
  - Review Committee, Draft Final Report, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 227)
  - Review Committee, Final Report, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 228)
  - Report of the View Committee, 1977 January (Box 35, Folder 229)
  - Implementation of the Recommendation of the Review Committee, 1977 (Box 35, Folder 230)
  - Report, TAC Quinquennial Review Mission to the International potato Center (CIP), 1977 (Box 35, Folder 231)
  - Draft Summary of Consultative Group Meeting, 1976-1977 (Box 35, Folder 232)
  - International Centre for Agricultural Research in the Dry Areas (ICARDA), 1977 (Box 35, Folder 233)
  - Cheek, Bruce, 1977 (Box 35, Folder 234)
  - International Research in Agriculture, 1974 (Box 35, Folder 235)
  - International Service for National Agricultural Research, 1977 (Box 35, Folder 236)
  - International Centre for Insect Physiology and Ecology (ICIPE), 1977 (Box 35, Folder 237)
  - Statistics on Expenditure, 1977 (Box 35, Folder 238)
  - General Correspondence, International Centers' Week, 1976-1977 (Box 35, Folder 239)
  - Informal Summary of Proceedings, 1977 (Box 35, Folder 240)
  - Calendar of Events, 1977 (Box 35, Folder 241)
  - Quinquennial Reviews, 1977-1978 (Box 36, Folder 242)
  - Donors, 1978 (Box 36, Folder 243)
  - International Rice Research Institute, Proposed Budget, 1979 (Box 36, Folder 244)
  - General Correspondence, 1978-1980 (Box 36, Folder 245-247)
  - Diary of Meeting and Attachments, 1979 (Box 36, Folder 248)
  - Summary of Proceedings, 1979 October 31-November 1, 1979-1980 (Box 36, Folder 249)
  - Programs and Budgets, 1979-1980 (Box 37, Folder 250-254)
  - Vacancies on Boards, 1979-1980 (Box 37, Folder 255)
  - Meetings, 1980 October 27-31, 1980-1981 (Box 38, Folder 256)
  - Reports and Correspondence, 1979-1981 (Box 38, Folder 257-258)
  - Vacancies of Board Positions, 1981 (Box 38, Folder 259)
  - Review Committee, Second Review, 1979-1981 (Box 38, Folder 260)
  - Programs and Budgets, 1981 (Box 39, Folder 261-262)
  - Reports of the Review Committee, 1981 (Box 39, Folder 263-264)
  - Meetings of the Board Chairman, 1976-1980 (Box 40, Folder 265-266)
  - General Correspondence and Reports, 1982 (Box 40, Folder 267-268)
  - Consultative Group Meeting, 1982 May 24-26 (Box 40, Folder 269-270)
  - Consultative Group Meeting, 1982 May 24-26 (Box 41, Folder 271)
  - Consultative Group Meeting, Related Materials, 1982 (Box 41, Folder 272)
  - Budget and Program Reports, 1982 (Box 41, Folder 273-274)
  - International Crops research Institute for the Semi-Arid Tropics (ICRISAT), 1982 (Box 41, Folder 275)
  - International Food Policy Research Institute (IFPRI), 1982 (Box 41, Folder 276)
  - West Africa Rice Development Association (WARDA), 1982 (Box 42, Folder 277)
  - General Correspondence, 1982 (Box 42, Folder 278)
  - World Bank Article, 1980 June 10 (Box 42, Folder 279)